http://www.pacificstatesfelt.com/privacy-policy.html

HomeCapabilitiesProductsMaterialsExample ProjectsEquipment ListAbout UsContact UsRFQCall:(510) 783-0277    Toll free: (800) 566-8866
E-mail:sales@pacificstatesfelt.net
CapabilitiesDie Cutting ServicesTape Slitting & Adhesives ServicesLaminating & Fabricating ServicesCustom Rubber Extrustions ServicesRubber Molding ServicesProductsCustom Die Cut & Lathe Cut GasketsCustom SealsCustom WashersCustom PadsStandard & Custom O-RingsHook & Loop ProductsMolded Bumpersexamples of workAssembly of Silicone Sponge Housing GasketDie Cutting of Foam InsertsDie Cutting of a Kydex Thermal Charger ShieldDie Cutting of EPDM Foam Housing Gasket
Print This PageEmail This Page
Tweet
Privacy PolicyPacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc. respects your privacy and our site visitors' information. We do not share, sell, or rent any of the information collected to any third parties and do not intend to do so in the future.Information CollectedIf you request or submit information to us by sending an Email via sales@pacificstatesfelt.net or by filling out a "contact" form, we may save your Email address as well as any other information you provide. This information may be used to contact you in the future by mail, Email, or phone to convey information about our solutions or services that we feel may benefit you. Your Email and other information will not be sold to any third party.Information Collected by OthersThis notice addresses only Pacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc.'s website policy, and does not apply to sites that users access via links from our site. Pacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc. is not responsible for the information collecting policies of other sites, for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our website, or for the information or content contained therein. Often, links to other websites are provided solely on the basis that they may contain useful information for our visitors. Users are advised to review the privacy policy of other websites.CookiesPacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc.'s website does not use cookies. Updating, Correcting, and Deleting Personal InformationIf you would like to have your personal information removed from our records, please send an Email with "Remove personal information" in the subject line.Legally Compelled Disclosure of InformationPacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc. may disclose information when legally compelled to do so: when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so or for the protection of our legal rights.Periodic Policy ChangesPlease note that Pacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc. reviews its privacy practices from time-to-time (i.e. to track technology and/or legal changes), and that these practices are subject to change. To ensure continuing familiarity with the most current version of our privacy policy, please bookmark and periodically review this page.This policy statement is made in the name of Pacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc. and is effective as of February 17, 2012. This statement does not create an agreement between Pacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc. and users, and as such, does not create any legal rights for any party.Contact Us:Pacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc.23850 Clawiter RoadSte 20, Hayward, CA 94545Toll free: (800) 566-8866Phone: (510) 783-0277Fax: (510) 783-4725Email: sales@pacificstatesfelt.net Website: www.pacificstatesfelt.net
Pacific States Felt & MFG. Co., Inc.23850 Clawiter Road, Ste 20, Hayward, CA 94545
Phone: (510) 783-0277Toll free: (800) 566-8866Fax: (510) 783-4725
E-mail: sales@pacificstatesfelt.netwww.pacificstatesfelt.net PrivacySitemapCopyright © 2012 Pacific States Felt & Mfg. Co, Inc, All Rights ReservedSite created by ThomasNet Web Solutions
